Well then.
Ladies and gentlemen.
What do you think?
Is anyone here yet?
All right, all right.
Well, in the meantime, I'll fix your bangs.
Oh, here comes "hello.
Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
Hello, hello, hello.
I'm so sorry.
Hello. Thank you.
Did you turn your head to the side?
Yes, it's back.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
He says he can see you.
Thank you, thank you, thank you. So, it's Sunday at noon.
I'm fine.
This is the Sunday tee time.
Hello, please. Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
Hello, ice, ice, ice.
It's Sunday.
Someone overslept.
I overslept. I'm watching this while waiting for the bullet train at Tokyo Station. Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you, Mr. Mitsuo.
The background is inorganic. It's all white.
Yes, it is.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
Yes, so...
T for T. Yes, that's right.
That's right.
Is that a hair in the picture?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hello.
Thank you very much.
Okay, well, I'll get right to it.
I'd like to start today.
First of all, everyone.
Ahoge ahoge, that's right.
In señorita.
Oh, here.
What are we going to do now? Yes! That's right!
I'm glad you commented, and today... the birthday party is over, so I'd like to thank you all again for coming.
I also want to thank those who came to the release event yesterday and the day before yesterday and those who couldn't make it to the live but wished me happy birthday.
I couldn't go to the Neko live, but there were many people who wished me happy birthday, so I'm really happy that June came.
Thank you very much.
I have WITH LIVE later today, but before that, I wanted to make some time for the live broadcast.
I know it was on such short notice, but thank you very much.
Happy birthday!
Thank you very much.
Oh, that's right, that's right.
And today, after WITH LIVE is over...
Yes, we're going to upload the video.
I hope you're looking forward to it.
Well... well...
It's your first time to do a youtube solo, isn't it?
It's a little weird. -I know, I know. It's nerve-wracking.
Congratulations on your 23rd birthday!
Thank you. I'm looking forward to Yuta's video too.
Yes, it's YouTube, today is YouTube I'm so happy for your birthday, thank you
Yes, the video that will be shown after the wiz live is over...
Oh, Minaka Aikawa, thank you very much for the lunchtime D. The video that will be shown after this is the video of the birthday party.
The birthday party was like watching a movie.
So you made a movie of it.
I'd like to upload it.
It's not the making of. It's not a making of.
It's not a making-of. It's really this story from the beginning to the end.
It's like this whole story from the beginning to the end is all put together in one video.
That's right.
The other four guys are saying it was so humiliating, it was like watching a movie.
And the other four, well, they were also, you know, movie-goers.
There were scenes in which the four of us appeared in the film as moviegoers, and we had a lot of help from the members and the staff.
The four of them in the 3D glasses are really moving.
And the popcorn!
Oh, my God, oh, my God!
It's popcorn from the East!
That's right!
I had a bite, and it was delicious.
Oh, Keiny-san.
23 Jaran!
Thank you very much.
Well, well, well...
A real movie theater.
Yes, it is.
So it's pretty big.
It was delicious.
It's from the East.
Yes, the East.
My beloved...
My beloved Touhou.
That's right.
It tastes like...
Caramel.
Salt.
Butter and soy sauce.butter soy sauce
so many things
You bought it for me.
Yes, he did.
He said they don't have those blue and red 3D glasses nowadays. You don't see that type of glasses in movie theaters, do you?
That's right.
He says he's a caramel guy. Caramel's good, too.
I was torn between the two, but I think I prefer butter soy sauce.
So you're a fan of the East.
Popcorn is so Eastern.
Um...
It's not buttery... they put butter on it.
That's right.
It's cold.
It's a chocolate latte, by the way.
Butter and soy sauce is good, right? Yes!
Yes, it is.
Iced tea in a teacup.
Where is it? Isn't it unusual to drink it?
Well, this, this, this... we have one in the office that comes out automatically in a paper cup, but...
But I found a teacup that looked like a teatime cup, so I borrowed it.
I see.
Thank you, Mr. Miyashiroishi.
Well... well...
You switched them.
Yes, I did.
We switched.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
So, this way.
Oh, this way, sir.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
It's spilling. It's spilling.
They put it in a cup, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's for show, yes.
It's, uh, it's Sunday tea time.
I'm having iced tea.
Iced tea is good, isn't it?
I know, I know.
He wants to squish it.
Squishy, YouTube's good.
It's good.
Okay.
Suddenly, suddenly, it's time for a quick shot.
Thanks for the teacups and the daily linner tea.
You know the vending machine that ran out of miso soup?
Did I ever tell you that? Yes, they ran out of miso soup.
Thank you for the tea I couldn't make it tomorrow.
I'll enjoy it. Thank you.
You've got a lot on your plate.
Thank you, Nonji.
It must be hard to take the extensions out now.
I won't be taking them off from now on.
I'm not taking them off from now on.
Yes, they're being stored in braids today.
Yeah, I'm watching while eating soba noodles.
I love it. I'm hungry.
I hope you enjoy it while eating lunch.
I'd love it if you could watch it while you eat lunch.
Suddenly, I'm back to the story of my birth.
This is my first time to play the drums.
I started with the drums.
I started out as a drummer in a band called "Crown's End".
I was in a band called "The End of Crown".
That's right.
They gave me a guitar and a tambourine.
Tambourines, that kind of thing.
Oh, and, Mr. Knuxet, enjoy the visual. Thank you.
Yes, Mr. Kraowa.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I guess we're all a little surprised to see you.
I've heard that name before.
It's the band that plays that instrument.
You know...
I wanted to put part of Crown Pop in the name.
Well, "clown" is a long name with four letters, so it was kind of hard to decide how to put it in.
The dance teacher had a suggestion, and we ended up with "Crown.
It says "Hello." Hello.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
He's asking if we're going to start a band.
You want to be in a band.
I do. I do.
Drama... drama and main vocalist.
Yes, yes, singing and drama.
We did that.
Your ears are getting red today.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's see...
Good morning. I've been wanting to try drumming for a while now.
I've been wanting to try my hand at drumming for a while now.
I'll be playing castanets.
I'll be there with castanets.
I think it's Sakho.
So that's why you're in the photo playing castanets.
That's right.
You've done a drama before?
I had a teacher teach me in elementary school.
That was the first time.
The drama was cool. Thank you.Drama was cool, thanks.
Looking forward to the day of Crapo live band!
Thank you, Atsuya!
But you know what?
Mr. Yusuke Fujiwara taught me how to do that.
I'm glad we managed to perform in front of everyone.
But the rest of the story was about the parallel worlds.
There's the world of idols and the world of bands, and in the world of idols, there's Clownpop.
I didn't expect... the reality isn't that clownpop.
The parallel world is called "Crown Pop." That's right.
It was interesting, wasn't it?
The world of change... Yes, that's right.
Popcorn.
I'm glad it was different from the usual.
It was good.
Yes, it was.
Yes, yes, yes.
Parallel poppers.
Yes, that's right.
So, Mr. Popper, you're supposed to be flying.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Uh, Crown.
When you're a fan of the end of Crown.
And when you're a fan of Crown Pop.
Oh, yeah.
Which one are you in now?
Right now, well, I'm still in the parallel universe.
I'm now as Rina from Crown Bop.
Yes, I am.
I'm sure I'll never come back.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't think so... I'm still in this world.
That's right.
Yes, you all will too, before you know it.
We will have a big screen in the back, so we will use images, and the images will change in time with the choreography, and then the choreographer will say, "Shoo, shoo!
It was a joy to see.
I was very happy.
Thank you very much for the dance drawing.
Yes, we projected silhouettes on the screen,
I did a lot of things.
Oh, I have to look for butterflies.
I asked him, "Tei-chan, did you used to dance ballet? I've only been doing ballet for about a year.
I've only been doing ballet for about a year.
I've dabbled in it.
Oh, Zuchi from Osaka...
That dance and video was really cool!
Thank you for being the main director!
Silhouette Morina, that's right, that's right!
That's me!
I see you did it, though!
Yes, a little bit, a little bit.
You didn't tap dance, which is your specialty.
Tap dancing, well... well, a little bit this time.
Well, you know, I had to go into hibernation.
I did a different kind of dance.
I see.
Yes, I've put it on hold for a while.
I'd like to do it again sometime when I wake up from hibernation.
It's summer.
Yes, it's summer. It's summer, but hibernation.
Yes, yes.
Which world do you do Japanese dance in?
I've already done Japanese dance.
Well, I'm kind of traveling.
I don't know when I'll be back.
I don't know when he will come back. It is in the southern hemisphere.
Yes. So, I have done it a little differently this time.
Yes.
You asked me to do a koumedaibi.
Suddenly....
Happy Birthday.
Suddenly.
Happy birthday.
Te-dee.
Hands. Thank you very much.
Happy birthday.
Thank you very much.
Eh, suddenly.
Eh~.
Thank you very much.
He's so cute.
It's so cute.
Look~. It's so cute.
Wow, wow, wow! I got so many!
I got so many!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! It's Doraemon!
I even got a present!
It's a Doraemon, but it's so cute!
Too cute! And I haven't seen any of your comments!
Thank you so much! It's so cute!
Oh, Doraemon!
Well, you said it was too sudden.
I'm so happy.
Look, it's so cute.
I heard that this changes color when you pour some of the lessons on it.
Did you guys hear that? It changes color.
What?
Well, I think I'll just eat some now.Well, let's eat a little now.
It still looked okay.
I'm gonna put it on, guys.
Okay, everyone, let's go.
Oh, they want to take a picture.
Okay, okay.
Oh, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Okay.
I got it.
Is it okay? May I? May I?
Ohhh, it's so cute!
Sure, please.
Too cute.
Wait a minute, everyone.
Congratulations!
Oh, they said OK. Thank you.
I'll put it on.
What color will it turn? I'm sure.
Here we go.
Watch out. Watch out.
They're all going.
I'm going to get on them.
He says it's dangerous.
I'm going to get them all.
I'm gonna call everyone.
I'm going to call everyone.
I'll call everyone
I'll call on everyone.
I'll pour it on everyone.
I guess I'll have to eat some of this.
Thank you very much.
Oh, the color that's getting darker.
I wonder if this is different.
Well, then...
It's purple... from blue to purple... the color has darkened.
The color has become darker.
It's a little hard to tell from the video.
It's so refreshing!
It's lemon. It's good.
It's so good!
It tastes like lemon.
It's delicious.
Citrusy. Yeah.
That's great. Thank you very much. Thank you for dinner.
I'm glad it's not eggplant.
Yes, indeed, indeed.
That's too funny.
I thought it was, but it was lemon.
Yes, it was lemon.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Eggplant-flavored sweets are the worst.
You're right, you're right, you're right.
I'm late. I just got here. Thank you.
I'm so happy!
They're calling it "eggplant and eggplant eats.
I don't like eggplant sweets.
I might not be able to eat it.
Other cakes are good, too.
Like this.
Mont Blanc. Mont Blanc, I think.
Yes.
And...
This way
This is this one.
Strawberries. So cute!
Pyramid-shaped Mont Blanc. Hey, I've never seen this before.
It's all so stylish.
I thought so.
Are all the plates from your office?
Yes.
Yes!
Yes, sir.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
Hey! I've never seen it before.
I'm glad.
Thank you all.
I guess Tokyo has fashionable sweets.
Indeed.
I've always wanted a birthday.
That's right. It makes me happy.
I wonder if this is something that has been used by a lot of big stars.
I'm curious.
I feel like eating summer pickles.
By all means, please eat them today!
I'm here to tell you that you don't have to say spacha.
While I'm not looking.
Let's go back up.
Congratulations to Anki!
And thank you for telling me about it.
Hmm?
Your toothbrush is pink.
I think it's Mr. Dalloway's mom-and-pop.I think it's Mr. Dalloyo's Momran.
My favorite cake.
Ooh!
I know you.
I know someone who knows.
Thank you.
They're coming tomorrow for my birthday too. I'm so happy.
That's nice.
The color's changed again. It's more purple.
I know it's hard to tell through the screen, but it turned purple.
I'll enjoy it later.
Oh, I see it.
That's great!
Of course, it's Chibara!
Thank you very much!
Today is the day of the purple festival.
You're all covered in purple, huh?
Thank you very much.
You're right.
Let's eat it later.
Yay! Thank you so much!
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Knuckle Z.
I'm so happy for you.
I'm so happy.
Grin, grin, grin.
You'll be full by the time we do WIZ LIVE.
I'm sure.
I'll be full.
I'm definitely full.
You're drinking hot drinks that are supposed to be cold.
I'm pretty sure these teacups look like they're getting hot.
I can't stop grinning.
You know, I think I'm gonna have a little taste of that.
I'm glad you're happy, Uti. Thank you.
He's saying he's getting a little nervous about the red-tailed water live. We're almost there.
We start in 25 minutes.
We'll start at 12:30. That's right, about two hours, give or take a couple of hours.
You can munch away during the WIZ LIVE.
I won't be able to talk.
I can't talk.
I'm looking forward to talking with you all.
I'll be there in about 50 minutes, so I'll have lunch and wait for you.
Oh! Have a good day.
Okay, so the time is divided into a little bit of seconds, so please be careful.
Please be careful not to make a mistake.
I couldn't buy it this time, so please do it next time.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to talk to you a lot. Of course. In my own clothes. Yes, in my own clothes.
I'll take it from here. I'm going to see the customer.
Good luck.
I'd be happy to watch you eat, but you know, I can't talk to you.
Hey...
I see. The first half starts soon. That's right!
So I am looking forward to talking with you all.
So, I talked lightly about Ikuta, but...
There will be a video after With Live is over, so I'd like you to watch it.
What do you think?
She's asking me what to wear.
What are you going to wear?
I think I bit something.
I bit him. Sorry.
I'm sorry. Looks like your addition's dyed.
That's right.
I bit you, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
Miz live, we can talk about whatever you want.
Sorry.
I think I'll go to Rinatai.
Thank you very much.
Perfect! I'll be wearing this.
I'll be wearing this.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm so happy.
Your ears are red.
They really are.
Yes, they are.
It's like this.
Mr. Nairy.
Congratulations to everyone who was born in the same era as Reati.
Thank you very much.
You know what, I'm getting really nervous right now.
That's a good kind of nervous.
I'm looking forward to it.
Hey, skirt.
Thank you.
I'm a little nervous, too.
I'm a little nervous, but I'm looking forward to it.
Nice nerves, yeah.
Thank you very much.
Relax!
Relax! Relax!
I hope I can relax with you all!
I'll be back in three hours.
Not so much yet.
I'm sure those of you who bought the extra tickets will be quite a bit further along.
Yes, I hope everyone has eaten and is ready and waiting for me!
Maybe when I sit down in front of my iPad.Maybe when I sit down in front of the iPad.
I'm sure everyone has a premonition of the nerves to come, but, you know, it's a countdown.
I'm nervous. I haven't changed anything, but I'm getting nervous on my own.
Please come talk to us when we launch again!
I've eaten dinner, I'm moving on.
I'll see you later.
Oh, I'm here wondering what I'm going to have for lunch.
What should I have for lunch, too?
Hey.
Mr. Teechan, you have 10 seconds.
Think about it.
Oh, okay.
I'll see you later.
Oh, I finished my steak and hamburger, so I'm all set.
Okay, then, everyone.
I hope you're all ready to go.
Well then, I'll get ready for WizLive.
I think I'll be done with the delivery soon.
I'm looking forward to talking to you for the first time in a year. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your time.
I'm sure you'll all have your pick of places to go and things to do.
So please be careful where you're going.
He said you need to stretch for Wiz Live. Yeah, you're right, I might need to prepare, stretch.
Also, YouTube, please deliver properly. Yes! Of course.
Thank you for the distribution. Thank you for watching too.
Hey, again, thank you all again for the congratulations and thank you very much.
See you later if you are going to meet me at WizLive later on.
Well, I'd like to go now.
Oh, you said you're going to get ready. Yes, I will.
Okay, bye. Thank you very much.
Bye-bye!